baking911.com 2015-06-12

# Privacy Policy | CraftyBaking | Formerly Baking911

#### 1\. Overview

Thank you for visiting www.craftybaking.com (the "Website") and reviewing our Privacy Policy. Your privacy is important to us, and our policy is simple: we will collect no personally identifiable information about you when you visit the Website unless you choose to provide that information. This Privacy Policy does not describe information collection practices on other sites, including those linked to or from the Website. As noted in our “Terms of Use,” which you are encouraged to visit, our Website provides these links as a convenience, and is not responsible for the contents or activities of any linked sites.

#### 2\. What Type of Information We Collect

We do not collect any personally identifiable information about you from our Website unless you voluntarily provide it. In some areas of Website, we may request that you provide us with personal information that will help us to provide you with information about our products and services, including your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, and other information from which your identity is discernible. For example, our Website includes, or may include, places where you can create a profile or account, or sign up to order a product or use a service.

When you visit our Website, we may also collect usage information describing how our Website is used and navigated, including the number and frequency of visitors to each section of the Website and the length of their stay. This information includes the domain names of users and browser types that visit our Website and the time of day the website was visited. This information is not personally identifiable information.

We also use cookies. A cookie is a small piece of data that is stored in a browser-related file on your computer's hard drive when you use the Website. Cookies are uniquely assigned to your computer, and are read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Our primary use of cookies is to improve your experience on our website. For example, storing a cookie on your computer allows you to login without typing an e-mail address, password, or other information each time.

#### 3\. Children.

In order to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13). If you have a child under the age of 13 that accesses our Website and provides us with personal information without parental or guardian consent, you may contact us to have the information removed from our records.

#### 4\. How We Use This Information.

When you voluntarily provide us with personally identifiable information, we will use that information for the purposes for which it was provided. In general, and except for the situations specifically described below, we do not share any information about you with anyone without your express consent.

We may use the information that you voluntarily provide to us to deliver to you information about our company, our Website, and the services we provide. For example, we may use your contact information in order to send you e-mail or other communications regarding new services or products that we are offering. We may also provide additional communications, promotions, or information on new business or marketing opportunities. In addition, you may receive free informational newsletters from us relating to sports, athletics, fitness, and other topics.

We may also use information that you provide to tell you about carefully-screened products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. Also, we may share our customer information with select companies whose products or services we feel may be of interest to our users. We do this because most of our customers enjoy being introduced to new or value-oriented products and services. However, you may opt out of receiving these communications at any time by following the instructions below.

The law requires disclosure in some instances. For example, we may be required to share information to protect against fraud, in response to a court subpoena, and the like. As we continue to explore new business opportunities, we may need to, and we reserve the right to, transfer and assign customer contact and site usage information collected on the Website to one or more affiliated and unaffiliated entities as part of a business transaction. In all such situations, we stress the confidential nature of the information being shared.

#### 5\. How to “Opt Out” of Having Your Information Shared.

If for any reason you do not wish to receive communications from our Website, just tell us. You can call us at 646-715-5881, or you can send an e-mail to Sarah@craftybaking.com. Also, we provide a direct link for you to easily opt out of our various e-mail promotions that provide information about the special opportunities we offer at the bottom of those e-mails.

#### 6\. The Security of Your Information.

Our Website has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, unauthorized access, and alteration of the information under our control. If you ever use your credit card in connection with purchasing goods or services from the Website, your credit card information will be protected through the use of encryption technology. Encryption technology makes it difficult for your credit card information to be intercepted or stolen while being transmitted.

While there is no such thing as “perfect security” on the Internet, we will take all reasonable steps to insure the safety of your personal information. However, we cannot guarantee the security of information provided over the Internet, and we will not be responsible for breaches of security beyond our reasonable control. If you have any questions about our privacy policy or information security, you can contact the Website’s customer service through the "contact us" section of the Website, or by contacting us in any of the ways described below.

#### 7\. Changes to Our Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy was last updated on March 4, 2014. We may update this policy from time to time as our information practices are modified or changed. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

#### 8\. Contact Information

Questions or comments regarding the Website should be sent by e-mail to Sarah@craftybaking.com.
